LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of
deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate
the face of light
Save your tears for the day
When our pain is far behind
On your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
Fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
Did you penetrate the Coast Guard's
surveillance net as planned?
Yeah.
They opened a hole right on time.
It's the real thing...
Now we're ready for war.
We didn't buy these to wage war.
These weapons are powerful enough to
be used for deterrence, instead of war.
Is that Comrade Kuze's teaching?
That's right.
I wouldn't know, since I've never met him.
I can't use the net, so...
is Kuze really a revolutionary?
I've heard rumours that he's got
Japanese blood in him, too...
We don't know whether or not
he's a true revolutionary,
but he has great ambition
and the ability to take
action to achieve his goals.
Okay, let's bring in the cargo.
Chain
of
Relativity
Fukuoka's electricity transmission
circuits will temporarily shut down
if two or more points on the high-voltage
transmission lines are over-stressed.
As a safety precaution in such cases,
the system is designed to default temporarily
to a backup line to provide electricity.
However, by prompting a unidirectional
electricity flow on the backup line as well,
the stress will trigger a
chain reaction of failures,
resulting in a massive blackout in the
capital, Fukuoka, within a matter of minutes.
It would be the same for any other city.
They are labourers who were
assembled to relocate the capital.
The refugees are thorough, aren't they.
Kuze must have taught them how
to trigger a massive blackout
and then leaked to the net that refugees
might launch a terrorist attack.
I see.
He is a worthy leader for the refugees.
He made them reconsider suicide bombings,
and instructed the refugees on ways to
achieve freedom with very little loss of life.
I have no idea how he tamed them
in such a short period of time,
but I can understand his thoughts very well.
Kuze, I'll prepare the best scenario I can for you.
It seems Dejima has declared
itself an autonomous region.
Yes.
Is that Kuze's doing?
Kuze has not shown himself,
but there's no doubt about it.
He is effectively using the net to
communicate the refugees' will to the media.
Nanyou News Agency is calling
him the refugees' Che Guevara.
An invisible hero, again...
What I don't understand is that he was originally
one of the Individual Eleven, right?
Why did the refugees accept him so easily?
Are we to believe that he
has some special ability,
just as the Major and Ishikawa have suggested?
We can only figure that out if we
catch him and ask him directly.
We only have jurisdiction
here because he's involved.
That's right.
We must first defuse this situation by capturing
Kuze, since he is leading the refugees.
After we accomplish that, we will secure the right
to challenge the Cabinet Intelligence Agency.
There's a lot of them down there.
Doesn't it have something to
do with the refugees uniting
in response to the sentiments expressed
by the rest of the population?
In this kind of situation,
the ones who are more desperate tend to be
faster at taking action and coming together.
In reality, the legitimate citizens' actions are limited
to demonstrations against various government agencies.
I guess we could say the citizens are progressively
pursuing a generalised particularism,
or rather, an ostrich policy.
Even though the refugees have
thrown down their gauntlets...
Let us into Dejima!
Open the bridge!
Batou, you guys are on recon.
Find out to what degree the
refugees have armed themselves.
I'll join you guys after Ishikawa and I
infiltrate the refugees' network and find Kuze.
Roger that.
We're from Section 9.
Seems the situation has got a lot worse.
The brass sure doesn't seem to think so,
even though it's not looking good here.
There are enough people who want to transfer
jurisdiction to their pet militias, too.
You guys came as part of that whole
deal, didn't you?
This is independent action, nothing else.
Hah.
It'd be nice to have the freedom
to do our jobs, like you guys.
Well, at least you have backup.
We need to hack a refugee's brain first.
It seems Kuze's cyberbrain
is open to the refugees 24/7.
Until we get close to his ghost
line, no backups are necessary.
Understood.
From the preliminary investigation
there do not seem to be
connections, such as cash flow,
between Chief Cabinet Secretary
Takakura and Poseidon Industrial.
I see.
Will we make the meeting?
It doesn't look like there
will be any problems right now.
Chief, we have news regarding the Foreign
Ministry worker whom you were to meet today.
What is it?
What news?
Sir, Niihama Police just reported
via the Kyodo News Agency
that he has been run over by a subway train.
I wonder what happened...
It seems there is something big hidden
behind the security pact as well.
Return to HQ.
Understood.
It's more active than I'd heard.
The refugees have been building on
these high-rise slums for over twenty years.
It's not altogether unwarranted of them to start
calling the high-rises their own "castles".
We'll split up from here on out.
I'll take Azuma and Yano.
Pazu, Bomer, Saitou and Togusa:
you guys form the other group.
If they have already secured weapons,
formed a militia,
and established a command infrastructure,
it'll be a lot harder to capture Kuze.
Understood.
We'll go hit opium town.
If they've been assembling a militia here,
opium use will be up.
All right.
We'll go check out the
black-market weapons dealers.
Understood.
Now, what's the shortest route to Kuze...
Major!
A female full-cyborg police
officer is currently on duty
in a police station in Dejima,
according to shift records.
Good work.
Pass me the visual feed.
Okay!
They sure look bored.
Aren't they on alert for terrorist attacks?
All right,
we'll borrow this woman's cyberbrain.
Roger!
It's kind of unnerving with
them sitting over there.
They'll hear you.
By the way, did you reformat
your right arm's control system?
Seriously, you shouldn't upgrade control software.
HQ to patrol sector 26, respond.
H-Hey.
That must be it.
Hey, what's wrong?
There it is!
It seems he's connected to Kuze this very instant.
Good, we'll trace this route
and confirm Kuze's position.
Roger!
Jeez, these cyborgs...
A firewall maze?
is he making it only accessible
to refugees via zoning?
We can't determine his current position.
The route's fixed.
so I think he's somewhere in Dejima.
Oh, that must be it.
A huge number of refugees are accessing
it, aren't they?
Still, aside from filtering I'm
not noticing any special firewalls.
What should we do?
All right, we'll all dive at
once, before the enemy detects us.
Prepare the Omni-sense mask.
Target: Kuze's visual field.
We will determine his location from what he sees.
The file on the Individual Eleven, huh.
Yes.
Right now, determining Kuze's
location comes first, though.
Ishikawa, create a backwards
feed on the net from Gate 5
and investigate the factors
that attract refugees to Kuze.
Roger.
Tachikoma, inject the mask array.
We will cross the ghost line with the Chroma file.
What is this...?
What a suffocating memory matrix.
Major!
You must hurry.
The Omni-sense mask is deteriorating rapidly!
Don't do it.
If you make a connection that
goes any deeper, you'll die.
He's already seen through the Omni-sense mask?
Offensive firewalls won't have any
effect, so don't bother attacking me.
That's not what I mean.
I'm saying that if you link to my
consciousness, you'll regret it.
Houeimaru
Is that it?
Major!
Tachikoma, what happened?!
Drop the connection immediately!
Roger.
Major, get a hold of yourself!
Major!
Tachikoma, was it an offensive firewall?
We don't know!
But we couldn't detect any
viruses or offensive firewalls.
We haven't been affected.
Could it have been some sort
of hallucinogen or stimulant?
I'd find it hard to believe that the
Major would fall for something like that.
Hey.
Major!
Are you all right?
What's wrong?
What did you see?
A delusion...
Never mind that.
More importantly,
determine his hiding place from
the information we stole from him.
Hurry!
Understood.
He's a formidable opponent.
He's on that ship right now.
In addition, I know him...!
Houeimaru
It's me.
Oh it's you, Kuze.
Did something happen?
I'm sorry...
but there is a possibility that there will be a raid
by the police or some military special ops force.
However, you shouldn't
needlessly engage in combat.
Hide your weapons and avoid
fighting as much as possible.
Please don't get yourself killed over nothing.
I'm not trying to be harsh here,
but I recommend this eyeball.
I see. Good stuff.
Aren't they?
I bet you didn't think you
could get body parts in Dejima,
but in reality, you can get almost
anything as long as you can pay for it.
Hey.
Can I have a joint, too?
I wouldn't if I were you.
Seems like it.
So, did Kuze change his body here too?
No, he didn't change.
Another specialised body like his can't be found.
I just replaced his skin.
And his face?
His face...
I had it made by some face maker.
It was one of a kind,
though the mouth barely moved.
I'm surprised you knew a face maker.
Anyone would be eager to make
a face for a guy like Kuze.
I'd be glad to do it if he were to come, too.
How does he attract such a following?
Eh, who knows.
It may be that we're randomly getting
drunk off the size of his ambition.
The size of his ambition...
Batou.
What?
I have Kuze's location.
He's at a camouflaged port on
the northeastern tip of Dejima.
There is a modified fishing ship moored there.
Houeimaru
He is probably on that ship.
This isn't like you.
The information's not 100% positive?
We were detected at the last minute.
Right now, we're circling above that port.
He hasn't left yet.
We will catch him before he gets away.
Rendezvous at the port ASAP.
Roger!
Let's move!
It's been settled.
Tomorrow, we'll have hope, at last.
Really?
I thought you'd be the one to do it.
We can do it!
It's a revolution.
Y-You're Kuze?
That's right.
Aren't you... one of the...
Individual Eleven?
Why are you a comrade?
You're an enemy who killed a legend, Densetsu!
Hey.
It is as you said,
I am one of the Individual Eleven.
Then... why does everyone accept you?
Well, listen a minute.
He's...
If you can't believe me, that's fine.
Human beings cannot fully understand each other.
For now,
it's enough that you realise
you cannot understand me.
My role is to guide you to
the same point where I am now.
However, I cannot demonstrate that with
words, only with actions.
If you are still not convinced
after seeing my actions,
you have the option of leaving voluntarily.
Houeimaru
Houei
What's going on?
Major, there are three boats.
They're probably making it easier to slip
by the Coast Guard's surveillance net
by camouflaging them in the same way.
The target is on one of them.
One of them?
She appeared to have been attacked
when she tapped into Kuze's vision.
Hey, are you all right?
Yes...
Sweep each boat in pairs.
Go with thermo-optical camouflage.
The pairs will be Batou and Togusa;
Pazu and Bomer;
and Saitou and myself.
Ishikawa, Azuma and Yano will be backup.
Tachikoma, keep watch from above.
He's not here.
Not here either.
A live broadcast relay machine...?
Watch out!
An ambush?!
Did you come here... to catch Kuze?
What?!
You fools...
Kuze... won't be caught by the likes of you...
He's... a real... hero.
Houeimaru
Why did they fight...
I told them not to die needlessly.
Major, what's going on here?
It's the first time we've had it this bad!
Kuze isn't here,
not to mention this was just an ambush
and we've let a rookie die!
I'm sorry.
Kuze... was never here in the first place.
He is in Ostrov Iturup to buy plutonium
from the Russian mafia.
Houeimaru
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(the time is right)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
I see inside,
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
all I need,
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.